Yeah, class is in session, let's go.
Time to get the grammar right, you know.
(Unit One, let's learn.)
How are you? I ask with a smile.
It's been quite a long and beautiful while.
I just got a brand new job on the street.
And there are so many people I want to meet.
You ready? I see the light in your eyes.
No need to overthink or over-analyze.
Yes, thank you, that's what we usually say.
Keeping it short and bright throughout the day.
We say 'I've lost my keys' when we can't find them now.
But 'I lost them yesterday' tells us exactly when and how.
It has been raining all week, and the puddles still remain.
But it rained last night means there is no more rain.
Do you have these? Yes we do.
Those are brand new just for you.
What are those? I need to know.
Where is the place that we should go?
We say three for ten to get a deal.
That is just the way we really feel.
Do you have these? Yes we do.
Always learning something fresh and new.
I went to work and I ate some good food.
I came home early in a wonderful mood.
How has your week been going so far my friend?
It's been going great from the start to the end.
I've been working hard every single day.
And I am tired but I will find a way.
I like to ski when the winter time is near.
It's my favorite sport to watch and cheer.
I might have the flu, I think I need to stay home.
You can't go return it when you are all alone.
Oh my gosh, look at the sky so blue and bright.
Everything is going to be alright tonight.
I will help you and we're going to succeed.
This is the knowledge that you really need.
Yeah, we're going to make it work out fine.
One more time let's sing along with this line.
Do you have these? Yes we do.
Those are brand new just for you.
What are those? I need to know.
Where is the place that we should go?
We say three for ten to get a deal.
That is just the way we really feel.
Do you have these? Yes we do.
Always learning something fresh and new.
(And that's Unit One, everybody.)
(Good job today.)